[Applause]
People of the world, welcome to the
giant. The visitor attraction for the
21st
century. The exhibition space featuring
the giant experience. A glorious
celebration of the great men and women
of your country. Inventors, artists,
scientists, celebrities, and
athletes. The viewing tower.
See the city from the shoulders of a
child. The roof
garden. New dimensions in retail,
gastronomy, and special events for
diversity of
occasions. The world's tallest moving
[Applause]
sculpture. Its head
moves. Its arms
move. It speaks and sings.
Pleased to meet you. A place to behold
heroes and
superheroes. A space to celebrate the
great and the good, the game
changers, the icons of your city and
country. Every hour, the giant
transforms into an extraordinary person.
from
sports,
science, characters, her favorite
heroes, and recites poetry and words of
wisdom to the crowds
below. A digital canvas for artistic
creation, a creative canvas like no
other. A digital art gallery in the sky
that displays masterpieces from today
and throughout the ages.
[Music]
The giant brings artists together from
throughout the
world. A beacon for brand
celebration. A new eye-catching platform
for businesses to reach customers in a
novel and memorable way.
[Music]
A giant
opportunity, a business model that
delivers worldclass
experiences and worldclass
profits. An economic
stimulator that enhances
tourism, job
creation, footfall and commercial
activity in the city.
Join the Giants
[Applause]
movement. The world's largest
selfie. An homage to human potential.
The world's most all inspiring
selfie. Visitors are scanned and
instantly become a
giant. An experience to share and
remember for a lifetime.
[Applause]
There's nothing like it on the
planet. Imagine you can be the giant.
Before we begin talking about what we
just watched there, the giant, I just
want you guys to understand that that is
a concept and there are people who are
saying that it's going to start becoming
a reality in 2025 or 2026. So there is,
at least to my knowledge, no giant that
actually exists, but it is conceptual at
this point. So with that being mind,
let's go to Genesis 11. Because when you
see the the the person going into the
the little scanner and they get their
body scanned and then their their body
is reflected on the image that is
standing many many stories above the
ground, you get a picture of a sense of
pride. And so the pride is what I want
to focus on here in this video because
in Genesis 11, all of the people were
one back then. And God goes down and he
sees what they're doing. And he that's
when he basically hit them with
different languages. But before the
different languages came, the people in
Babel said, "Come, let us build
ourselves a city and a tower whose top
is in the heavens. Let us make a name
for
ourselves." Now, this is basically what
men want to do. This is what mankind
wants to do. We are so incredibly
prideful that we want to make a name for
ourselves. And this is in complete
contrast to what we should be doing. If
you pay attention to what John the
Baptist says in John chapter 3, I think
it is, he says, "He must increase and I
must decrease." And so if you're paying
attention to the propaganda and what the
world is telling you to think and
telling you how to think. If you buy
into what they are saying, then you are
going to make things about you. They are
not about you. They are not about me.
They should all always be about God
because it's all about him. He's going
to get all the glory anyways. And so
this is just watching that giant and to
see people's image being up on that
image. you are just seeing all kinds of
biblical applications that just are
popping off of the screen. I'm sure when
you watch that video. Another
application is what I'm sure many of you
guys think about is in Revelation 13
where this is during the great
tribulation. This begins the great
tribulation in a sense. It says he was
granted power to give breath to the
image of the beast that the image of the
beast should both speak and cause as
many as would not worship the image of
the beast to be killed. And so the false
prophet is who is going to be granted
power to breathe life into this image.
And so many people speculate that the
image, whatever it's going to be, nobody
knows, is going to be somehow connected
to AI. And so I am one of those people
who also can see it that way, just from
my understanding right now, right here
today. Anyways, there is an image that
is going to be erected and this is going
to be put into the temple. Now, I don't
know if it's that image, the giant,
because I think it's too tall, but
there's going to be something similar to
it. And so, that's really fascinating,
but pride is always going to be at the
center of everything. It's pride, pride,
pride, pride, pride, me, me, me, me, me.
And so, when you think about pride and
you think about sin, there are people
who are so so much wanting to hold on to
sin and it's because of their pride.
There are people who will not let go of
sin because it's they have an
unrepentant heart. And because they have
an unrepentant heart, that is because of
pride. And so this is why we are told to
lower ourselves to clothe ourselves with
humility. Because the people who hold on
to their sin. They're like, I'm going to
let go of that, that, that, and that,
but I'm holding on to this, this, this,
and this. They know what they should let
go of, they just are not. And that is an
unrepentant heart because of pride. And
this is why God hates pride. Proverbs
6:16-1 17 mentions all of these seven
things that God hates and the very first
thing that he mentions is pride. And so
you're seeing how all of this is coming
to be and it is just fascinating when
you look at what's happening right now
or something that could be happening
right now and you apply it to the world.